[theme music playing]
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
TAEUN HOTEL. JEJU
[General Jang] In three days
the US president's youngest daughter
will arrive in Jeju Island.
She's scheduled to be there
for only a week.
But intel suggests that individuals
we think are linked to al-Qaeda
are planning to kidnap her.
The issue is the girl is refusing
a security detail.
saying it's a matter of privacy.
So we booked the room below hers
for unofficial protection
until she leaves the country.
[receptionist] Good morning. sir.
How can I help you today?
Room 1306. I'm checking in.
Okay. Let me just look it up. sir.
Uh. sorry. but it looks like someone else
has already checked into Room 1306.
Who's in it?
I'm not allowed
to disclose guest information. sir.
[rock music playing]
[device beeping]
[static]
Okay.
-[device beeps]
-Otter One. wiretap's ready.
[General Jang] Can you turn off
that stupid music. you idiot?
[sighs] You nutjob.
Then is Room 1506 available.
So sorry. sir.
Looks like Room 1506 has someone
checked in there already too.
[beeping]
Location tracking complete.
[straining]
I should install this in the car too.
GPS on steroids.
[chuckles]
SAMGEORI TRADITIONAL GUKBAP
GUKBAP SPECIALTY RESTAURANT
-[waiter] Sit anywhere you like.
-[customer] Okay. Thank you.
[waiter] Welcome back.
Love the hair. as always.
What can I get you?
-[Jin-cheol] One sundaeguk. please.
-[waiter] Sure. Coming right up.
It's been a while. 66.
Can you please go change.
But this is who I am inside.
What's wrong with how I dress?
You look ridiculous.
Hey. I'm not the one
with the same black hat
that every generic spy wears.
Despite that. I'm not judging you
for what you decided to wear
'cause I don't care.
Now that's ridiculous.
I don't know if that's the right word.
You're thinking of "idiot".
Hey. I don't want to be seen with you.
Go sit over there.
You can't sit here. Hey!
Geez.
Man. don't talk to me.
Don't even look at me.
We can't afford to blow our cover
-so can you please stop fooling around.
-[scoffs]
You need to be careful too.
Until this mission's over.
we all need to be like a ghost.
Invisible. okay?
Then why did you show up in that?
Well. excuse me for being proud
of our culture.
You're an idiot.
-Right back at you.
-Double back at you.
-Triple back at you.
-Quintuple back at you.
No. wrong.
You said "quintuple." you idiot.
Yeah. quintuple. you idiot.
[Han-soo] Right. so you're supposed
to say "quadruple." you idiot.
[Jin-cheol] This idiot can't count.
-I said. "Right back at you."
-Yeah!
-You said. "Double back at you."
-Then. "Triple back at you."
-Yeah!
So what comes after that. you idiot?
Quintuple. you idiot.
That's enough!
I don't know why you idiots
were sent on this mission too.
but it doesn't matter.
Stay out of my way.
If you mess around like this
during the mission…
I will make you answer for it.
Wow. that's some next level audacity. man.
Hey. North Korea.
You've been a thorn in my side
since the start.
So. how about this?
Want me to take you to the border?
-What you say?
-[Jin-cheol laughs]
Was that excitement in your voice?
I bet it is.
Let's get you home. fucking idiot.
You son of a bitch.
Hey. be the bigger man.
He clearly has no manners
so just ignore him.
"Manners"?
Hey. tae kwon do.
You're just mad
that you're pretty much useless.
What?
If you watch him fight.
you can feel how hard he trained
in the North.
What about you?
You fight like you're doing choreography.
Probably can't even break a board.
[bowls clattering]
Man.
Your brain isn't wired right.
Are there no manners in your code.
you robot?
Sounds like this discount rock star
can't keep his mouth shut. can he?
Stop breaking tables and come outside.
-Famous last words?
-Just come out. punk.
[exclaims]
[both exclaiming]
Rock and roll!
Didn't I say not to mess around?
What's that saying again?
Two's company and three's a riot.
Hey. Major. You sure about that?
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
[thunder rumbling]
Over here! There's someone here!
Hey! Wait!
Wait!
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you for stopping for me.
You guys are lifesavers.
What an unexpected gift.
The stars have aligned in our favor.
She just dropped right into our lap.
[Guk-cheol] Get to the rendezvous point
as fast as possible. Dismissed.
[phone buzzes]
1 NEW MESSAGE
[Sang-a] Min-ji is in a vehicle
going down Highway 87.
It's registered to Juhak Construction.
[Kim] Juhak Construction…
Did Ju Gang-chan send you?
Well. we just moved her
after we got a call
from Ju Gang-chan's daughter.
[scooter horn honks]
Like father. like daughter. right?
Who's daughter is she. huh?
Han-soo.
Min-ji's alive.
Thank goodness.
Okay. Let's go. That way.
[bodyguard] Mr. Nam.
Cho still hasn't come out yet.
He's just taking care of the bodies.
He'll come when he's done.
Han-soo. does this thing go any faster?
I'm at full throttle already.
You expect more speed
with two grown men on this thing?
[straining]
[phone buzzes]
We got a location!
Mususan. 247.
Clean her up and take her to the study.
Yes. sir.
-What are you doing?
-Uh… Oh.
I was about to call home. sir.
Do it later.
-Shall we?
-Oh. okay.
Right this way.
Have a seat.
Min-ji. how are you feeling?
Are you okay?
It was raining so hard.
I didn't even recognize you.
Oh. it's okay. And I'm fine.
What on earth happened to you?
Why were you out there?
Uh…
Sorry for fighting with your daughter.
And thank you…
for helping me despite that.
No.
I wanna know how you ended up there
in the street.
Uh…
Well…
Everything's a little hazy.
It all started with waking up
in a freezer though.
So I ran as soon as I could.
You got out of the freezer
on your own. huh?
Yes.
Remember anything before that?
That day in the principal's office.
So what exactly happened in the warehouse?
Was anybody else inside?
Uh. yes. There was.
Someone who looked like a thug.
I'm not sure who he was.
I've never seen him before.
Did he try to talk to you at all?
No. sir.
He chased me with a knife
without saying anything.
But I got away.
He shouted at me as I ran.
but I couldn't hear what he said
because of the rain.
Can't believe you got away.
Actually…
would I be able to use your phone. sir?
My dad will come right away.
I can't let you do that.
Sorry?
The thing is…
my daughter wanted you dead.
So what should I do as her father?
I don't remember anything.
[stammers] I d… I don't know anything.
As you get older. you'll learn to lie
more convincingly.
'Cause I don't know if I buy
this performance you're putting on.
What performance?
I don't know what you mean. sir.
I already know everything.
I even know that you pretended
to fall asleep in the car.
Such good luck…
My Hye-ri was definitely born
under a lucky star
seeing how the girl
just fell into our lap.
[panting]
I seriously don't know anything! I swear!
Let go of me! Let go! [whimpers]
KIM MIN-JI
[Min-ji crying]
I love and cherish my daughter
more than anything.
Enough to clean up her mistakes.
[Min-ji whimpering]
'Cause she'll always be my little girl.
If really you think about what she did…
it wasn't even that bad. right?
So here's the story we will go with.
Some thug kidnapped Kim Min-ji
just outside the high school.
Then both went missing.
[straining]
The thug's been taken care of
so that leaves you.
All I have to do now is erase you
from this world.
Please. sir.
[whimpers] Dad!
Please!
Please don't kill me!
I won't say anything!
-[doorbell rings]
-[Min-ji crying]
[ringing]
This is the only access point.
What should we do?
What are we? Girl Scouts?
[gun cocks]
-Ram through it.
-Yes. sir.
Three unidentified vehicles
have breached the gate.
Who are you people?
Do you know where you are?
If you don't get the hell out right now.
I'm gonna…
I don't really care what this place is.
As you can see.
we're on official business.
You have a girl here. don't you?
We need to take her with us.
Sir. three unidentified vehicles
have just entered the premises.
-Go hide her in the basement.
-[henchmen] Yes. sir.
No. wait! Sir. please!
Please. no! [screams]
[Guk-cheol] Find her!
CALLING… DEPUTY CHIEF OF NATIONAL SECURITY
IM DO-HYEON
[Do-Hyeon] Why hello. Chairman Ju.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
I'm sorry. sir.
You're in here by yourself.
but you set up this chair like this.
Maybe you had a guest over.
Juhak Construction's chairman.
Ju Gang-chan's your name. right?
Yeah. that's my name.
And who are you?
Well. let's just say
I'm a civil servant. hmm?
I doubt you're with the police.
The NIS?
Or maybe the SMD?
[chuckles]
You seem to know a lot for a civilian.
It sounds like you play golf
with people in government.
-Hmm? [chuckles]
-[Ju chuckles]
Let's stop wasting our time then.
I'm the director
of the SMD of South Korea.
And I'm looking for a girl
named Kim Min-ji.
I tracked her to this location.
I know she's here.
so hurry up and bring her out now.
Listen.
You can barge in here.
break down the gates.
I don't care.
But I can't stand smoking.
Hey. shithead. I guess you can't tell
your head from your ass
'cause I've been treating you civilly.
Bring me Kim Min-ji
while I'm still asking nicely.
Just how much power does
your agency actually have?
Enough that you can bust in here
and threaten a civilian like this?
Hey. Ju Gang-chan.
Don't you see
the deep shit you're in. huh?
My agents have your house surrounded.
This operation's sanctioned.
you little shit.
-No luck?
-She's not in any of the rooms upstairs.
Not in the basement either.
-[agents grunting]
-What's that?
[grunts]
[grunts. groans]
Don't move.
You guy's are trespassing.
This is private property.
This operation's sanctioned!
Stop or I'll shoot!
You don't have the balls.
[Han-soo] Damn it.
Looks like the SMD folks beat us here.
What should we do?
Well. I guess it doesn't matter
who goes first.
-Ready to go inside?
-We can't.
The SMD and Ju Gang-chan.
they both want her for their own reasons.
If we rush in without a plan.
it would put her in more danger.
So we're just gonna stand by
and do nothing?
Wait. Aren't those the people
who helped us earlier?
Let's split up.
You go ahead.
[grunts. groans]
[coughs]
Seems to me that you're the one
who's in deep shit now.
[phone buzzing]
-Yes. hello Minister.
-[minister] You idiot!
What the hell are you doing there?
-Sir?
-[minister] Leave now!
-But sir…
-[call ends]
Get up. We're leaving.
[agent groans] Okay. Sorry. sir.
[stones crunching]
[shushes]
[sighs]
How much did he cough up
to have a government official
in his back pocket like this?
[Guk-cheol] Damn it.
Everyone. fall back!
SUNG HAN-SOO
[dramatic music plays]
All clear.
[shushes. mouthing words]
[grunting]
-Who's that?
-What? [laughs]
Hello. gentlemen!
Dry cleaner at your service
Looks like we got a wrinkle.
but we'll iron it out. [chuckles]
[shouts]
-[groaning]
-[electricity buzzing]
Min-ji!
Min-ji! Hey. Hold on.
[grunting. muffled]
You okay. Min-ji?
Mister. what are you doing here?
[panting] The dry cleaner's
is temporarily closed.
Are you okay? Think you can walk?
-Who are you?
-I'll explain later.
-I don't understand what--
-It's okay.
-We have to go.
-Come on.
Hurry.
Good work. you two.
-Get her in.
-Yes. sir.
Kim Min-ji. please come with us.
-Who are you?
-It's okay.
[Min-ji] Mister. Who are these people?
Wait. sir!
See you back at the office.
-[door closes]
-[engine starts]
Any updates?
It's been quiet here. No movement.
Have them watch the rear just in case.
-We're heading back first.
-Yes. sir.
All vehicles. watch the rear
until Vehicle 1 arrives at HQ.
Okay. Copy that.
Hey. sir?
Thanks for saving me.
But who are you guys?
Where are we going right now?
Let me contact my dad.
Or I'll jump out of the car.
[door handle rattling]
Min-ji.
You'll be fine.
but you have to trust us. okay?
-Please. just let me call my--
-Okay.
It's okay.
[Guk-cheol] We can't tell you who we are.
That's just the nature of this job.
We live in the shadows.
A life where people don't know you exist.
Out of sight. in the background.
Nothing to report.
[grunts]
What the heck? Where'd he go?
Shit. [breathes heavily]
-[gun fires]
-[groans]
[groaning]
Where the hell did they take my daughter?
They're going back to HQ. [groans]
[radio beeps]
[Kim. distorted] Min-ji. Min-ji.
Can you hear me?
What's he saying?
-Try another channel.
-[Jang] Yes. sir.
Min-ji. Can you hear my voice?
Don't worry. everything will be fine.
I'm coming to get you.
Min-ji. are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Min-ji!
I can hear you. Agent Kim.
If you so much as lay a finger
on my daughter.
I'll kill all of you.
[Guk-cheol] Wow. what a time to be alive.
This is what freedom looks like in Korea.
A goddamn spy having the nerve
to threaten the SMD Director.
As soon as I get her back…
I swear I'll surrender.
[Guk-cheol]
Yeah. I remember what you said.
I just don't know
if I can trust a spy's word.
Turn yourself in first
as a sign of good faith.
Can't do that until she's with me.
Fine. I can play hardball. too.
I'll keep your daughter company
while we wait. huh?
If you want to bring a housewarming gift.
I love a good whiskey.
[Kim] All right.
I'll bring you the strongest I have.
[chuckles] Can't wait.
I'm already getting a bit thirsty.
You better come at me
with everything you've got.
I'm just saying.
isn't this taking it too far?
Using a kid like this? Huh?
This is wrong.
[sighs] What the hell am I saying?
[breathing deeply]
I am an agent.
I'm not a dry cleaner.
That's not who I am.
No! What I am… is an agent.
I am an agent. I just work
as a dry cleaner. but I'm an agent!
[groans]
I need to get myself together.
ONCE A MARINE. ALWAYS A MARINE
[groans]
Tae kwon do.
[screams. distorted]
I should've snapped both his scrawny legs.
[gasps. screaming]
[beast growls]
Attention!
Hey. pookie.
Honey. what are you doing here?
A-And what's with the knife. sweetheart?
Well. you haven't come home in three days
so I came to see if you started
a new family or something.
Ah. geez.
[grunts]
But judging by the looks of things.
it doesn't seem like
you're cheating or anything.
What? Why would I cheat on you?
Do you think I'm crazy?
I-I mean. you promised in our wedding vows
that if I ever cheated on you.
you'd have me shot.
I accept that answer.
So then. what's your excuse
for staying out for so long. soldier?
Yes. ma'am!
You know I'm not the type of guy
to stay out all night.
But Kim's daughter was kidnapped
out of nowhere.
[distorted] You know Min-ji. right?
Why was she kidnapped?
That's a long story.
But anyways. I was in the holding cell.
so I got there late.
And then there were some bad guys
who insulted our daughter.
-What?
-[normal] That's what I'm saying!
Why bring up Da-bin?
[distorted] I should've taught them
a lesson then and there!
But the police showed up
and tased me. [imitates Taser]
Man. I forgot
how much Tasers actually hurt.
And then Han-soo was there!
He was trying to help
but fell into the water.
[laughs] I didn't know
he was such a bad swimmer.
Anyway. so I was on my way… Wait a sec
But first I went to a rest area
and bought a germanium bracelet…
Didn't get me one?
[normal] Oh. actually. this one's for you.
[distorted]
I don't know if it works. though.
So. anyway. I crossed mountains
and rivers just to make it here.
Why did I come here? 'Cause…
[normal] Oh. right!
The weapons! [chuckles]
I'm here to get the weapons.
Hold on.
Kim's daughter was kidnapped. so you
and Sung Han-soo are going to go with Kim
to try to rescue his daughter?
Exactly! Man. you're so smart.
Oh. my wife is such a genius. [chuckles]
So. yeah. I was thinking of going…
-but I really shouldn't.
-[beast growls]
Forgive me. ma'am.
-Who the hell beat you up like this?
-It was self-inflicted. ma'am.
Help him.
Like…
I can go?
You guys went to war together
No matter what I say. you're gonna go.
Just bring me tteokbokki after.
Extra sauce.
Spiciness level two. ma'am?
Add some cheese too.
Cheese! Got it!
And will you please go change
out of your clothes? You smell.
Ugh. What is that?
Whatever. I don't care.
Don't worry. I'll be safe. okay?
Why would I worry about you?
I'm more worried
about the idiots you're fighting.
When will you guys realize
you're too old for this?
[sighs]
I love you. ma'am.
Attention!
[exhales heavily]
Oh. my goodness.
I almost died.
That could've been it for me.
Took ten years off my life.
[grunts]
With cheese.
Okay. Level two spicy with cheese.
With cheese. With cheese.
Spiciness level two.
[grunts]
My babies.
You've been asleep too long. huh?
It's time to wake up. Ah.
You doing okay? Hmm?
[sniffs deeply] Ah. I love the smell
of gunpowder in the morning.
Smells like victory.
All right. who wants
to have some fun? Hmm?
Who wants to come with?
Who's the lucky winner?
Is it you?
If I take this one with me.
then this one will be sad.
I don't want to hurt anyone's feelings.
[sniffs. yawns]
Hard to focus when you haven't slept well.
Okay.
First. we take a Claymore.
M3.
Man. I missed you.
The 249.
Hey. baby.
You feel left out?
Fine.
You're comin' too.
Okay. Hell yeah.
You know what? Let's just all go.
Oh. yeah. now it's a party!
[laughs]
Take us to the maximum-security wing.
Copy that.
[tires squealing]
-Take her to the interrogation room.
-Yes. sir.
Situation room. do you read?
We are on full emergency alert.
effective immediately.
Is the tactical unit here yet?
No. but they'll be here soon. sir.
I've watched too many Hollywood movies.
Who do I think I am.
sneaking in like this?
[grunting]
What is this? The tactical unit?
Are we going to war or something?
Agent Kim said he'd surrender
as soon as he found his daughter!
[Sang-a] You know
the director doesn't trust him.
He won't let his guard down
until Kim is out of the picture.
or he turns himself in.
I know. but don't you think
this is unnecessary?
It just means Kim…
is someone the director fears.
SMD PARKING LOT
EVACUATION ROUTE
INTERROGATION ROOM
HIGH-RISK MONITORING ROOM
MECHANICAL ROOM
Interrogation…
[siren wailing]
SECURE HOLDING ROOM
INTERROGATION ROOM
CLEANING SUPPLIES
Ee-moh!
Auntie. you still work here?
[chuckles] It's been too long. huh?
[chuckles]
It's your nephew.
Don't you remember me? [chuckles]
You're okay. right?
You can still breathe well?
Okay.
Ma'am. again. I'm really sorry.
I'll make it up to you. I promise.
[grunts]
The mechanical room.
The mechanical room. Where are you?
I know you're here…
The…
Which way is it again?
It's…
this way.
Is it?
OIL GEAR PUMP - GENERATOR TANK PUMP
ELECTRICAL ROOM EXHAUST VENT
How many of these do I need?
There we go.
[humming]
Now we go back to the interrogation room.
[gasps]
[breathes heavily]
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Where am I?
Hello?
[Jang] Tell us what your name is.
What?
[breathes shakily] It's Kim Min-ji.
Why are you doing all this?
Kim Min-ji.
How much do you know about
what kind of person your father is?
My dad?
I mean…
He's just a guy who works at an office.
Why?
Did my dad do something wrong?
Is that why you're doing this to me?
Give me that.
[clears throat]
Agent Kim's daughter. listen closely.
Your dad's a spy.
sort of like a secret agent.
-You understand?
-Director.
[Guk-cheol]
He's probably the most notorious one too.
So if your dad's true identity
gets exposed.
the North will send operatives down.
And if that happens.
it becomes a huge headache.
Not to mention how much trouble
he's already caused trying to find you.
Why did this man
who's been a ghost for over a decade
come back with such fury?
Because of his daughter.
So here's the thing.
You and your father have put me
in an extremely tough spot right now.
which is why I need to know
the whole story.
I want you to tell me every last detail.
Like why in he hell were you
at Ju Gang-chan's house?
And what exactly are your dad
and Ju Gang-chan plotting to do?
It's important
that you're honest right now. okay?
Am I clear?
Ju Hye-ri.
Hye-ri and I got in a fight.
Who's Ju Hye-ri?
Ju Gang-chan's daughter.
I remember fighting with her
then something hit me and I passed out.
A brick… [sighs]
I think that was what…
When I eventually came to.
I was in a warehouse freezer.
And it was…
It was really scary. but I got away.
I was taken by Hye-ri's dad after that.
So what you're saying is…
Agent Kim caused all that trouble
after a decade hiatus
to point where the North even
sent an operative.
Because of what. exactly?
All over a kids' playground fight?
[chuckles]
[chuckles] Oh. Agent Kim.
So my dad…
He's a spy?
Sir.
The Deputy Chief is here.
Did he say why?
I'm guessing Ju Gang-chan contacted him.
Shit.
Go hide the kid.
-Yes. sir.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
DEPUTY CHIEF OF NATIONAL SECURITY
IM DO-HYEON
[breathing heavily]
Why is this so hard?
I feel like I got
the short end of the stick.
Or am I just whining? [panting]
Finally.
[grunts]
-Huh? There it is.
-[door opens]
Wait. Where are they taking her?
INTERROGATION ROOM
I just got here.
[groans]
[sighs]
Where are you assholes taking her now?
I'm so tired.
[sighs. groans]
ISOLATION ROOM A
Hey. punk!
Trespassing on private property?
Seriously?
Are you trying to get yourself fired?
Which room is she in?
[Han-soo] Min-ji.
Kim Min-ji.
Up here.
It's me. Uncle Han-soo.
[gasps]
Uncle Han-soo?
How did you know I was here?
[Han-soo] Shh.
I'm going to open this now.
You have to be quiet. okay?
[grunts]
You must've been so scared.
It's time to go see your dad.
That's it.
Use the bed. then you should be able to
reach my hand.
Ready? And one. two. three.
[grunts]
Bring the girl here.
Now!
[scoffs] Aw. geez. [chuckles]
Ju Gang-chan has you
under this thumb too. huh?
I wonder how much your honor was worth.
What was that?
So what's gonna happen to the girl?
You're going to hand her over
to Ju Gang-chan. right?
Is it because Kim's daughter knows
your dirty secrets?
Have you lost your mind?
You need to get your head outta your ass.
Agent Kim's obliterating everything
in his path looking for his daughter.
And both you and that idiot Ju Gang-chan
are finished if you give up his daughter.
So will you please…
shut up and stay out of my way
until I take care of Agent Kim.
you useless motherfucker!
Okay. now. we need to turn right.
-Oh. okay.
-Yeah.
Go straight.
[electricity crackling]
You're doing great.
[sighs]
[panting]
We can't stop here.
We're almost there. okay?
-Uncle.
-Yeah?
They said my dad's a spy.
Did you already know that?
Your dad…
Yes. he was a spy.
But it's different now.
Hmm?
What do you mean?
-[alarm blaring]
-So what is he now?
Min-ji. I'm sorry. but we have to hurry.
Think we can talk about this later?
-Okay.
-All right.
-Let's go.
-[sniffles]
[alarm blaring]
What is it?
[operative] Alpha Tango 312.
-Alpha Tango 312.
-What's going on?
-Alpha Tango 312. We need backup.
-What do you think? There's a situation.
[operative] Emergency alert.
I repeat. emergency alert.
Talk to me.
[operative 2] It's a complete blackout
in the Maximum Security Wing.
-[operative] We need power now!
-Generators are coming online.
Where's the repair team?
[Han-soo] Careful.
Wait.
It's here.
I'll go down first and catch you.
Uncle.
Huh?
Come on.
I promise I'll catch you.
It'll be fine. Come on. trust me.
Put your feet down first.
Just like that.
It's okay. take it slow.
Okay. I got you.
Ready? One. two…
-Three!
-[gasps]
ZONE C BUNKER
ACCESS DENIED
[door lock beeps]
What's wrong?
Min-ji.
How are your acting skills?
What?
[grunting]
[gasps]
[Han-soo] Hold the door.
Okay.
Let's go.
[clears throat]
Come on.
Put your hands on your head now!
Uncle.
Ah. geez. Why's he always so late?
-Hey. Sung Han-soo.
-Hmm?
Agent Kim said he'd send the strong stuff.
-Is that you?
-[chuckles]
Well. we prepared a little something.
What do you think?
It's a pretty good gift. right?
Uncle.
What do we do?
Min-ji.
If you look to your left just behind you.
you'll see an emergency exit.
When I count to three.
I want you to run to it
without looking back. okay?
But Uncle Han-soo…
-What are you gonna do?
-What'll I do?
I'm just going to say hi to those guys
and catch up with you later.
I can't just leave you here. Uncle!
Okay. one…
We can say Han-soo was killed by accident.
We only need Min-ji.
Two…
Uncle!
[rock music playing]
Fire in the hole!
-Three.
-[gasps]
[screams]
What the hell?
He's always late.
Flash-bang out.
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[Guk-cheol grunting]
-Smoke grenade.
-[tires screech]
Here!
[all coughing]
-Open fire.
-[Min-ji groans]
[coughing]
[Guk-cheol] Tactical Unit!
Converge on the Zone C bunker!
Hey. get in!
I know you showed up late
just to look cool.
Min-ji. don't worry. We're okay.
Whoo! What's taking so long? Get in!
Hey. genius. how can I do that
when it's still locked. huh?
Please unlock the door!
[guns firing]
Shit.
-These are blanks. right?
-No!
They're blanks.
Whoa!
-Hey. get down!
-[Min-ji screams]
They're blanks! Return fire!
-Min-ji. hi!
Oh. come on! Not the tires. please!
[groans]
Hey. you seriously only brought blanks
to this gun fight?
You should've brought
some live rounds too!
They figured it out in two minutes!
[Jin-cheol] I did bring live rounds. man!
But I can't kill those guys.
they're my juniors.
Will you guys cut it out?
[Min-ji screaming]
We can't stay like this.
Here.
Choose a gun!
I love them both too much
to decide which one I wanna use.
-So you decide.
-You wanna scare her even more?
Cease fire!
Hey. Park Jin-cheol.
You done?
Do you surrender?
[Jin-cheol] This is a white flag.
We surrender!
We're coming out. so don't shoot!
Here I go!
Slowly!
Slow down!
Easy. easy!
Why are there so many of you?
You need a small army
to catch the three of us?
I can't believe I saved you from drowning
and you used live rounds.
There's a kid here. you idiot.
You two came back to your old
stomping grounds with your guns blazing.
Should I do nothing?
Take her.
-Yes. sir.
[Do-hyeon] What the hell?
Everyone. drop your weapons!
Did I stutter?
Drop your weapons right now!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[ominous music playing]
[choking]
[rock music resumes]
Dad?
Dad!
Wait here.
Min-ji.
I'm here now.
Let's go home.
Dad…
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
[Kim] Don't worry. Min-ji. I'm here now.
[Jin-cheol. Min-ji scream]
I need to see this through to the end.
[Jin-cheol] Take a nap.
Just let it go. hero!
[Kim] Attempted cover-up. kidnapping…
Why don't we take this opportunity
to get rid of him first?
[Gang-chan] I can only imagine
how desperate
you must have been to find your daughter.
[Sang-a] After today.
he will never see his daughter again.
[Min-ji] Dad!
[Kim] I would do anything for Min-ji.
including…
getting rid of you.